{
    "id": "ee5ae8bddd4346218d41fd499ca06e6a",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You had better ...................... a specialist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "consult",
                "consulted",
                "to consult"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "335dfc5e5bec41e296a31616783b6bf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must not leave books near the open fire. They …………………. easily.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "catch to fire",
                "catch with fire",
                "catch fire",
                "catch on fire"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9020c725131c41a2b283dc17c650af35"
        },
        {
            "question": "When will the meeting .......................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "be held",
                "be hold",
                "hold place",
                "take hold"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e470ffbd576f425a88f704767881d2a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s ………………… this weekend. It is snowing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go ski",
                "go skiing",
                "go to ski",
                "skiing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3249f5b3b7d349cd8220a0c0c54ac6e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have had ..................... for a bit. I am going home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough Rome",
                "enough of Rome",
                "Rome enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "797ad4728a224a41ac5567f590774c09"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is trying to make a machine that would ………………….. people in wheelchairs to get up stairs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "able",
                "enable",
                "capable",
                "unable"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa4d915bc1fb489fba15e6b25465ac4c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I really ..................... . when I went skiing last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enjoyed",
                "enjoyed myself",
                "enjoyed with",
                "enjoyed myself with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef26c77a727b47e6b621e06a76f2e50a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I felt like ..................... .",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cry",
                "to cry",
                "crying",
                "to crying"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "51f5d8d16980421cae764c95b766de31"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... for hours, and I was getting tired.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was running",
                "had been running",
                "have been running",
                "am running"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "daaafa7004a148c5badd6d7098c44cb7"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................., he went on working.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As he was tired",
                "Tired he was",
                "Tired though he was"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1fbd8f77f6914155823d0691f068027f"
        }
    ]
}